https://westphysics.com/home/privacy-policy/

Request a quote * = required field Cancel
Please fill out the form below to have a West Physics representative contact you to arrange for a service or product quote for your facility.
ZIP / Postal Code
AfghanistanÅland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongo, Democratic Republic of theCongo, Republic of theCook IslandsCosta RicaCôte d'IvoireCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEswatini (Swaziland)EthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and McDonald IslandsHoly SeeHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestine, State ofPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRéunionRomaniaRussiaRwandaSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint MartinSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth GeorgiaSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands, BritishVirgin Islands, U.S.Wallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabwe
Country
Brief Description of Service or Product Needs*CAPTCHA
This iframe contains the logic required to handle Ajax powered Gravity Forms.
Our address and telephone numbers are:
West Physics
3825 Paces Walk SE
Suite 250
Atlanta, GA 30339
770-435-9186 • 1-866-275-WEST (9378) • FAX 770-599-2333
Office Hours: West Physics maintains liberal office hours for the convenience of our customers nationwide.
Monday-Friday:
9AM – 8PM Eastern Time
8AM – 7PM Central Time
7AM – 6PM Mountain Time
6AM – 5PM Pacific Time
Closed Weekends & U.S. National Holidays
Request a quote
Privacy Policy
WEST PHYSICS CONSULTING, LLC, (“West Physics Consulting”, “West Physics”, “we”, “us” or “our”), a Georgia Limited Liability Company, is the owner and operator of this web site (the “Site”). BY UTILIZING THE SITE AND ENTERING INFORMATION ABOUT YOURSELF OR YOUR BUSINESS, YOU (THE “USER”) HEREBY AGREE TO BE LEGALLY BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AS AMENDED FROM TIME TO TIME. IF THIS POLICY IS NOT ACCEPTABLE AND YOU ARE UNWILLING TO BE BOUND BY IT, PLEASE DO NOT ENTER ANY INFORMATION ABOUT YOURSELF OR YOUR BUSINESS THROUGH THIS SITE.
Commitment to Privacy
West Physics respects the privacy of every individual who uses this Site. This Privacy Policy outlines the information West Physics will collect and how we will use that information. Therefore, please read this carefully before entering any information about yourself.
Personally Identifiable Information
When you visit this Site, we will not collect any personally identifiable information about you (such as your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address) unless you provide it to us voluntarily. If you opt not to provide us with personally identifiable information, no material consequences will result, although you may be unable to submit information requests through this Site.
Use of Personally Identifiable Information
West Physics may store and process your personally identifiable information in order to better understand your needs and to learn how to improve our site and services. We may also use your personally identifiable information to contact you (for example, we may send you marketing or promotional materials or other information, we may respond to your comments or requests for information, we may ask you for feedback on our site and services or we may contact you if needed in the course of processing your requests). West Physics may also use your personally identifiable information in accordance with any agreements that you may have entered into with West Physics. We may also enhance or merge personally identifiable information with data obtained from third parties for any of the foregoing purposes. West Physics will not give or sell your personally identifiable information to any outside organization for the organization’s own use without your consent. Your information may be shared with agents or contractors of West Physics in connection with services that these individuals or entities perform for West Physics. Nothing in the Privacy Policy shall be deemed to prohibit West Physics from disclosing your identity or information if West Physics is required by law to do so.
Security
West Physics will make reasonable efforts to keep secure the data you provide us and will take reasonable precautions, such as using a secure server, in an effort to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse or alteration. Agents or hosting contractors of West Physics who have access to your personally identifiable information in connection with providing services for West Physics are required to keep the information confidential and are not permitted to use this information for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for West Physics.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information Collected Automatically
In some cases, West Physics may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser or computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the website from which you linked to our site, or general demographics. West Physics does not collect personally identifiable information automatically, but we may tie information collected automatically to your previously submitted personally identifiable information. West Physics does not employ the use of cookies on this site.
Contacting Us Regarding Your Personally Identifiable Information
If you have submitted personally identifiable information through a West Physics website, or if someone else has submitted your personally identifiable information through the foregoing, and you would like to have that information deleted from our records, please contact West Physics via e-mail at info@westphysics.com, or send a letter to us at West Physics Consulting, LLC, 3825 Paces Walk SE, Suite 250 Atlanta, Georgia 30339. We will then use reasonable efforts to remove your personally identifiable information from our files, unless we are entitled or required to retain it pursuant to other agreements or by law. You may also contact us through either of the above methods to request the personally identifiable information that West Physics has collected about you through its websites. West Physics will use reasonable efforts to supply you with this information and correct any factual inaccuracies in this information. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email or regular mail as stated above.
Changes to Privacy Statement
Because of changes in Internet technology and practices, this Privacy Policy, and our Terms of Use and other policies may change from time to time. Please consult this portion of the Site for important changes to the Privacy Policy as they occur. Unless otherwise provided in an agreement between you and West Physics, by using the Site after West Physics posts any changes to this Privacy Policy, you agree to accept those changes, whether or not you have reviewed them, and such acceptance shall be deemed legally conclusive. If at any time you choose not to accept the terms of this Privacy Policy, you will not use the Site and enter information about yourself or your business.
Links to Third Party Sites
West Physics will have no liability for any personally identifiable information (including credit card information) entered on third party sites navigated to by the user from the Site. West Physics has every intention of providing links to only proven, secure sites from the Site, but cannot be responsible for any information entered by the user on a third party site.
No Liability for Acts of Third Parties
Although West Physics will use reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. West Physics will have no liability for disclosure of information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. In addition, West Physics will release specific information about you to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute or court order. We will also release specific information in special cases, such as if there is an attempted breach of security or a physical threat to you or others.
Home
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
Sitemap
Testimonials
We have been using West Physics since 2013 for our ACR accreditation and state testing requirements with MRI, CT, X-ray, Ultrasound, and mammography and have been very pleased with their ability to support our needs.  The physicists are knowledgeable and always interact well with the staff at our imaging centers.  Their response time for retesting mammography units when a tube or detector has been replaced on short notice has always been prompt to minimize our downtime.  Our staff enjoys working with this vendor!
— Siobhain Sullivan, MBA, RT(R)(CT)(MR)
Associate Director of Imaging Services
Rhode Island Medical Imaging, Inc.
East Providence, Rhode Island
Thanks again for the GREAT service provided with our multi-state outpatient imaging centers. Your help in keeping up with the ever changing regulatory environment throughout the accreditation process has made my job so much easier. It is nice to be able to direct my efforts into other important company initiatives while West Physics handles the dirty work.  Your team has been helpful in providing information when needed and serve as a great asset in keeping our centers accredited and operating within the rules. Thank you for all your help.
— Dan Balentine
Chief Operating Officer
American Health Imaging, Inc.
Atlanta, Georgia
West Physics replaced our dedicated in-house staff physicist that retired in 2013 and has been able to meet our expectations for all of our equipment testing and RSO needs since taking over.
The West Physics staff has been very responsive and flexible with all my department staff when they need to speak promptly with a physicist regarding their equipment or radiation safety issues.
I would recommend them to any hospital that is looking for a full service medical and health physics provider.
— Judy Canal, M.S.
Director of Imaging Services
Lowell General Hospital
Lowell, Massachusetts
"Thank-You. It has been a true pleasure working with your company and the physicists. The turnaround time for the reports is phenomenal. The physicists did an excellent job, so self-sufficient."
— Dorothy Meduna
Director of Radiology
CHI St. Joseph's Health
Dickinson, North Dakota
"Just want to let you know I got word today that we passed, maybe you already know. I would like to thank you and Zach and anyone else who helped this along. We have used West Physics for if not 12 years, then 10 and this is why. I feel you guys did an excellent job and would still recommend you to anyone, hands down. All your time and efforts need to be recognized, so again thank you."
— Tim Hof
Chief MRI Technologist
Cookeville Regional Medical Center
Cookeville, Tennessee
"This was our first experience with the ACR accreditation process and we had already been notified that we had not passed our SPECT QC performance criteria using a different Physicist Group. Our MRI department recommended West Physics, and I couldn't have been happier.
From the moment I called, the Staff at West Physics were friendly and professional, and completely understood my concerns and time constraints that I was facing to re-submit my data. When the physicist came to my facility, he was friendly, thorough and professional, and his knowledge of my camera was unsurpassed. I was extremely pleased with West Physics, and I appreciate all their help with our facility passing the ACR! We will always be using West Physics for all of our ACR Accreditation needs in the future."
— Anthony Feigum, B.S.R.T., CNMT
Chief Nuclear Medicine Technologist
CDI – Alexandria
Alexandria, Minnesota
"I’ve known Geoff West personally for several years. His company provides a quality service at a fair price. If you are going to make the effort for ACR site accreditation, then physics support is a must. I highly recommend West Physics."
— Wm. Faulkner, B.S.,R.T.(R)(MR)(CT), FSMRT
William Faulkner & Associates, L.L.C.
Chattanooga, Tennessee
"West Physics Consulting has been providing our Physicist Services since January 2007. As an outpatient PET/CT Imaging Center we require standard services (quarterly audits) as well as assistance obtaining ACR accreditation. The services that they have provided for our facility are excellent; I appreciate their attention to detail as well as personal service. I fully trust the competence and expertise of West Physics. It has been my privilege to work with the staff of West Physics."
— Sheryl Wilhite, CNMT, RSO
Chief PET Technologist
Decatur PET Imaging
Decatur, Georgia
"Having to go through accreditation on 3 brand new modalities seemed to be a messy and stressful process. I was wrong! West Physics made the process so easy and manageable that I will never stress out about it again. It was so wonderful to be able to complete the surveys on a weekend with little downtime and to have such a highly qualified cross trained physicist to be able to handle not only CT and MRI, but PET as well. I have recommended West Physics to other centers we work with and know without a doubt that they are the gold standard in Physics Services and Testing."
— Robert Moya, R.T.(R)
Chief Technologist
Via Radiology
Seattle, Washington
“I've been throwing your name out there a lot lately. I've been dealing with quite a few physicists that have not done MR testing before. When a site calls for their yearly testing I usually just tell them to call you since we have a high level of confidence in your ability and your familiarity with our product. Keep up the good work!”
— Senior Applications Specialist for a major MRI vendor
